racingjunk.com 2005-03-03

# RacingJunk.com Privacy Policy

**_GENERAL STATEMENT_**

RacingJunk.com is a classified advertising service. You do not need to be a registered RacingJunk.com member to view this web site. However, there are some features that are only accessible if you are registered. This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") discloses the privacy practices for Raceway Media, LLC ("Raceway"). Raceway is committed to your privacy. Raceway hereby notifies you of: 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours, or third party personally identifiable information is collected from you through RacingJunk.com. 
  2. The company collecting the information. 
  3. How the information is used. 
  4. With whom the information may be shared. 
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information. 
  6. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

**_INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE_**

Raceway is the sole owner of the information collected on RacingJunk.com. Raceway will not sell, share, transfer or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Raceway collects information from its users on every classified ad page as well as on the "Members", "Post Ad", "Modify Ad", Honor Payments", "E-mail Newsletter", and "Forum" pages. 

If you would like to place an ad on RacingJunk.com, some of your personal contact information is shown with your ad, including your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, and any other information that you specify. 

There will be a link from your ad that users can click on in order to e-mail you if they are interested in your ad. 

Prior to the expiration of a listing, Raceway will e-mail a reminder to the seller that the listing must be updated, renewed or deleted. 

If you click on a classified ad, this will bring up a page that asks for your Classification Number, Password and e-mail address. An e-mail can then be sent from you to the user who placed the ad. Raceway does not use this information for any marketing purposes. 

If you "Save To Favorites" an ad, that ad will be stored on your behalf for future access. 

When you provide RacingJunk.com with a testimonial about your RacingJunk.com experience, we may ask for your name, e-mail address, phone number, and feedback regarding your experience. We may use this information to contact you regarding your testimonial. If you indicate that we may quote you, your name and experience may be shared with others or posted publicly to our site and you may be contacted about your experience. 

**_REGISTRATION_**

In order to use all the services of RacingJunk.com, a user must first complete the "Member Profile" registration form. During registration, users are required to give information such as name, address, e-mail address, age, gender, online purchase habits and income. Mailing address and e-mail address is primarily used to confirm the identity of the user. This information is also used to contact the user about the services on RacingJunk.com for which he/she has expressed interest. Information as to the age, gender, purchasing habits, and income level and other unique identifiers (such as interests) are requested to help Raceway provide a more personalized experience on RacingJunk.com. 

**_OPT OUT PROCEDURES_**

You always may opt out of receiving future mailings or other information from Raceway. To request that you not receive future communications, please send an e-mail [to optout@RacingJunk.com](mailto:optout@RacingJunk.com) indicating the type of information that you no longer desire to receive. 

**_CHOICE/OPT IN_**

Users who no longer wish to receive the Raceway e-mail Newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt out of receiving these communications by updating their profiles on the "Member Profile" page of the web site. 

**_COOKIES_**

A cookie is data stored on the user's computer. Use of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on RacingJunk.com. Once the user closes his or her browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on RacingJunk.com, the user would not have to log in a Password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, he or she may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user may be limited in some areas of the RacingJunk.com site.  Cookies can also enable Raceway to track the interests of RacingJunk.com users to enhance the experience of the RacingJunk.com site. 

Some of Raceway's business partners may use cookies on Raceway's site (for example, advertisers). Usually, these cookies exist only if the user links on the ad. Raceway has no access to or control over these cookies. 

**_LOG FILES_**

Raceway may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

**_SHARING_**

RacingJunk.com does not rent, sell or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you have requested, when Raceway has your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  1. Raceway may share aggregated demographic information with its partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 
  2. Raceway may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, Raceway will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. Per Raceway's contractual arrangements with partners, these partners are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the explicit purpose of providing these services. 
  3. RacingJunk.com shall respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise its legal rights or defend against legal claims. 
  4. RacingJunk.com believes it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to physical safety of any persons, violations of RacingJunk.com's Privacy Policy, Terms of Use and Guidelines, incorporated herein by this reference, or as otherwise required by law. 
  5. RacingJunk.com shall transfer information about you if RacingJunk.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, RacingJunk.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

By using RacingJunk.com and its various features, you may make some of your personal information public or you may choose to share some of your personal information with others. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

**_CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY_**

Raceway takes all necessary precautions to protect users' personal information both online and off-line. 

However, Raceway is not responsible for the confidentiality, security or distribution of your own personal information by our partners and third parties which occurs outside the scope of your agreement with Raceway. 

Raceway shall not be liable for the transfer of any personal identification information resulting from loss or distribution of data, the delineation or corruption of storage media, power failures, natural phenomena, riots, acts of vandalism, sabotage, terrorism or any other event beyond Raceway's control. 

**_LINKS_**

Raceway may contain links to other sites. The linked sites are not necessarily under the control of Raceway. Please be aware that Raceway is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. Raceway encourages users to be aware when they leave RacingJunk.com and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. If you decide to access any of the third-party sites linked to this site, you do this entirely at your own risk. Any links to any partner of RacingJunk.com should be the responsibility of the linking party, and Raceway shall not be responsible for notification of any change in name or location of any information of the site. 

**_CHILDREN'S AND MINOR'S PRIVACY_**

Raceway strongly encourages parents and guardians to supervise the online activities of their minor children and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers to help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools also can prevent minors from disclosing their name, address, and other personally identifiable information online without parental permission. Although RacingJunk.com is not intended for use by minors, Raceway respects the privacy of minors who may use the Internet. Whenever Raceway becomes aware that a user is under the age of 13 years, the following additional terms, conditions and notices apply to use of RacingJunk.com: 

  1. Users under 13 years of age may not submit information through RacingJunk.com. Raceway will not enroll as a member any person under age 13, nor will Raceway collect any personally identifiable information about a person that Raceway determines is under age 13, except with written consent from the person's parent after informing the parent about the types of information Raceway will collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances it will be disclosed. 
  2. "Personally identifiable information" collected from minors may include any of the information disclosed in membership enrollment, including name, address, e-mail address, age, gender, income and other unique identifiers, and may be used by Raceway for the same purposes as adult information, as described in this Privacy Policy. 
  3. A minor's parent or legal guardian may request Raceway to provide a description of the personally identifiable information that Raceway has collected from the minor, as well as instruct Raceway to cease further use, maintenance and collection of personally identifiable information from the minor. 

**_SPECIAL OFFERS_**

Raceway sends all new members a welcoming e-mail to verify password and e-mail address. Established members will occasionally receive information on [OPTIONAL: products, services, special deals, etc.]. Out of respect for the privacy of RacingJunk.com's users, we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our "Opt Out" section above. 

If users wish to subscribe to Raceway's newsletter and/or periodic correspondence, we require their e-mail addresses. If they are under 13 years of age Raceway will not send them a newsletter. 

**_SITE AND SERVICE UPDATES_**

As necessary, Raceway may send the user site and service announcement updates. Users are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. Raceway communicates via e-mail with users to provide requested services and to resolve issues relating to their accounts. 

**_CORRECTION/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION_**

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as ZIP code), or if user no longer desires Raceway's service(s), he/she can update his/her profile on the "Member Profile" page of the RacingJunk.com web site. RacingJunk.com will endeavor to correct, update or remove the personal data provided by the user. 

**_NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES_**

If Raceway decides to change the RacingJunk.com Privacy Policy, Raceway will post those changes on the RacingJunk.com Homepage so users are always aware of what information Raceway collects, how Raceway we uses it, and under what circumstances, if any, Raceway discloses it. If at any point Raceway decides to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, Raceway will notify users by way of an e-mail. Users which have provided personally identifiable information before the changes in the RacingJunk.com Privacy Policy will have a choice as to whether or not Raceway may use their information in this different manner. If the user chooses that Raceway not use his/her personally identifiable information in accordance with the new Privacy Policy, Raceway will use information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was originally collected. 

Raceway will notify you of any significant changes to the RacingJunk.com Privacy Policy by sending you an e-mail notice. 

**_RECOMMEND AD_**

If a user elects to use RacingJunk.com's referral service called "Recommend Ad" to tell a friend about the RacingJunk.com site, Raceway asks for the friend's name and e-mail address. Raceway will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting the friend to visit the site. Raceway stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail. The friend may contact Raceway at info@RacingJunk.com to request the removal of this information from Raceway's database. 

Copyright ©2005 Raceway Media, LLC. All rights reserved. 

| 

| 

  **TESTIMONIAL**  
  
---  
  
"I sold my Barracuda through your web site within five hours. I listed it on a Sunday afternoon and had made contact with the eventual buyer by Sunday evening. The cash was in my hand and the car was gone by the following Saturday. I am forwarding you my honor payment. - Thanks"  
  
Jim
